All right, y'all. So, I did my roots. I
had to. It's been, you know.
But, what I did get in the mail
from the TikTok shop
is
hair gloss. And we're going to do it.
And we're going to use it. So, I have
regular shampoo that I'm going to use.
And then I'm going to use the share as
gloss as a So, after shampooing, apply
to damp hair from the roots to tips.
Leave in for 10 minutes, and then rinse
out. So, we're going to do it. Let's go.
Ooh.
Well, that smells good. Kind of.
And I'm one of those people that uses a
lot.
So, I just rinsed out my
color, but we are going to
put this on, let it sit for 10 plus
minutes,
and then we'll rinse out.
Just get it nice and in there. Does it
look nice?
>> More in the back.
>> Yep.
Nice and lathered it up.
Beautiful color, though.
>> Mhm.
>> Make sure it's nice and glossy.
>> I'm working in the back a little more.
Mhm.
>> Okay.
Let it sit for 10 minutes,
and then we will rinse it out.
Here we go.
Well, that's bleeding.
>> My whole boob fell out.
>> Oh, we got a uh-oh. We got a boob.
Get her in there.
Get her in there. Hold this. Hold this.
Hold this. We'll censor her out right
there.
>> [laughter]
>> That was funny. I wasn't ready for that.
>> That's great.
>> It smells really good.
>> The tiger smells like vanilla.
>> I got to put the pasties on.
Does it look like that?
>> Stop. Wait. Let me zoom back in. I I
zoomed out and it was it was all it was
all this one.
>> Does it look good?
>> Yeah, it does look good.
>> All right. Do I look like I have to wash
anywhere else or is it good?
>> No, you got it. I'm good.
>> Water, [music] I'm good. And my mood is
winning like a shoe. Keep spinning. Big
tripping. Trip tripping. All star
[music] vision. At Mo Digits. Exclusive
with the business. Always winning.
Better go go get it. Better [music] get
it. Better go go get it.
Better get it. Go get it. What you
waiting for? Better get it. Better go go
get it.
Go get it. Go [music and singing] claim
it. What you waiting for?